Double-click to open the Precious Files folder and find the F Adding Pledges in Scene Details.
Double-click on Box Pledges and drag it to the 2D or 3D window.
Double-click on the Avid file and drag it to the Female VR folder.
Double-click on the FVR Fifi folder and drag it to the 3D window.
Use the Edit Pledges tool in the 2D window.
On the center line in the front and back, right-click on the Pledges and select Open Edit Pledges.
Open the other half of the Pledges.
On the top of the Pledges, it shows the 2D Pledges.
Your mouse will select the 5th Pledges from the 2D Pledges toolbar and lock the outline of the Pledges.
On the 2D Pledges, select thetalent tool and drag to the center line in the 3D or 3D window.
Click on the Rely Pledges tool and drag the center line to the center line.
On the 2D Pledges, select the Flip Folder and tilt the fold block.
Click on the 2D window next to the skirt board and move the mouse.
The arrow will follow the light and indicate the direction the fold will be folded.
Ensure that the arrow passes through the entire skirt board.
Double-click to complete the setting direction.
When the fold fold button pops out of the window, select the character.
Then click OK.
Repeat the operation of the skirt back panel.
The mouse will stop at the 5th in the 2D vertical tool bar.
Select Lock the outer outline of the board.
Unlock the outer outline of the board.
In the 2D tool bar, select the fold fold tool.
Move the mouse along the outline of the board.
Stop when the fold line reaches the side.
This is the front part of the fold line.
Click on the fold starting point on the skirt board.
And drag the mouse along the outline of the board.
In the last section, you can see that there is a mistake when folding.
This is because the fold fold tool is folding in the default 13 lines to make a fold.
When Ctrl-Z is not folded back,
Use the free fold tool to fold the most part of the fold.
This is the last section.
Use the fold fold tool again.
Move the mouse along the outline of the board.
Stop when the fold line reaches the side.
This is the front part of the fold line.
Click on the fold starting point on the skirt board.
And drag the mouse along the outline of the board.
In the place where the fold stop,
Click the left button to complete the fold line.
Use the line split tool to fold in other points.
Press the nome는데 on the puzzle,
and use the mouse to move to other places.
Again,
press the mouse click the Brady loop.
Now,
From the mouse, select the fourth tool bar of the 3D full-fledged tool bar.
The single display arrangement point will be displayed around the virtual model around the 3D window.
In the 2D window, select all the panels in the frame, or select all the panels in the control plus A.
Move the panel up to show the arranged point that is blocked.
Arrange the panel to the arranged point.
Adjust the position of the panel in the purple bar bar arranged by the shape editor.
Adjust the position of the greenちはso that the circle is in evenly.
Open the control and press the left mouse button.
to make it easier for you to fold.
Activate the simulation.
When the folding simulation is complete,
remove the print from the skirt version.
Select the skirt version.
Right-click on the menu and select Remove Print.
Now we can see the simulation is complete.
To create the simulation,
click on theuchi.org
to create the simulation.
Now, select the simulation as the desired model.
Select the simulation in which you want to create it.
Double-click on the model to create the simulation.
Let's take a look at the simulation.
In this simulation,
we can use a point-shaped ruler for the model form.
Let's first see how it works.